centerstatebank.com 2008-09-10

# Privacy Policy - CenterState Bank

**Account Disclosures**

 **Privacy Mission Statement**

At CenterState Bank, our mission is to meet the desires of our customers. As financial service professionals entrusted with sensitive financial information, we respect the privacy of our customers and are committed to treating customer information responsibly.  Our Customer Information Privacy Principles serve as standards for all CenterState Bank employees for collection, use, retention and security of individual customer information.

 **Introduction**

 _We, our_ and _us_  when used in this notice, mean CenterState Bank.

This is our privacy notice for our customers.  When we use the words _you_ and _your_ we mean all of our consumer customers who have a continuing relationship with us, such as:

  * Deposit account 
  * Loan account 
  * Individual Retirement account 
  * Safe Deposit Box 

In this notice we will tell you the sources for nonpublic personal information we collect on our customers.  We will also tell you what measures we take to secure that information.

 _Nonpublic personal information_ means information about you that we collect in connection with providing a financial product or service to you.  Nonpublic personal information does not include information that is available from public sources, such as telephone directories or government records.

An _affiliate_ is a company we own or control, a company that owns or controls us, or a company that is owned or controlled by the same company that owns or controls us.  Ownership does not mean complete ownership, but means owning enough to have control.

A _nonaffiliated third party_ is a company that is not an affiliate of ours.

 **Customer Benefits of Information Management Practices**

We collect, retain and use information about customers only where we reasonably believe that it will help administer our business or provide products, services and other opportunities to our customers.  We collect and retain information about customers only for specific business purposes.  We collect nonpublic personal information about our customers from information we receive from them on applications or other forms; information about their transactions with us, our affiliates, or others; and information we receive from consumer reporting agencies.  We use information to protect and administer customer records, accounts and funds; to comply with certain laws and regulations; to help us design or improve our products and services; and to understand customer financial needs so that we can provide them with quality products and superior service.  Except as described below, we will not disclose a customer's private information unless instructed by the customer to do so.

 **Maintenance of Accurate Information**

We continually strive to maintain complete and accurate information about customers and their accounts.  Should a customer ever believe that our records contain inaccurate or incomplete information about them, they are encouraged to notify us.  We will promptly investigate our customers' concerns and correct any inaccuracies.

 **Limitations on Employee Access to Information**

Each CenterState Bank employee is required to follow our Bank's "Code of Conduct", which states that all customer information is considered private and privileged and is to be used only to provide our customers with the finest service available.  We restrict access to nonpublic personal information about you to those employees who need to know that information to provide products or service to you. 

**Protection of Information  
via Established Security Procedures**

We maintain physical, electronic and procedural safeguards that comply with federal standards to guard your nonpublic personal information.  Our employees are trained to understand and comply with these information principles.

 **Maintaining Customer Privacy in Business Relationships with**

 **Third Parties**

When we do provide customer information to a third party, we will require – through a written agreement – that the third party adhere to privacy principles similar to CenterState Bank's.

 **Providing Privacy Information to**

 **Customers and Responding to Inquiries**

At CenterState Bank, we value our customer relationships.  We want you to understand how we use the information you provide and our commitment to ensuring your personal privacy.  If you have any questions about how CenterState Bank protects confidential information, please call the Main Office at (863) 291-3900 or visit your local banking center.

|  Created on 2007-06-01 15:30:32 by admin  
Updated on 2008-07-09 14:22:37 by jason  |    
---|---
